coverawards.com 2008-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Mark Pasetsky's Cover Awards

Coverawards.com Media Privacy Policy  
Last Updated: January 14, 2008

**Coverawards.com** Mark Allen & Company LLC/Tecktonik Media/coverawards.com and all their affiliates (collectively referred to in this Privacy Statement as “we” or “coverawards.com”) recognize the importance of protecting the information provided by users of our website. Coverawards.com has implemented this Privacy Policy to govern the use of personally identifiable information that we collect from this Site (“Personal Information”). This Privacy Policy does not govern Personal Information collected from any other source or in any other manner.

**Overview**  
This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with information as to: (i) the type of information that is collected, (ii) how the collected information is used and with whom it is shared; (iii) how we intend to protect the information; and (iv) how you can have such information modified and/or removed.

**California Privacy Rights**  
Under California law, California residents who have provided personally identifiable information to a company may have the right to request a list of all third parties to whom that company had disclosed such information for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, along with a list of the categories of personal information that had been so disclosed. However, if a company adopts and discloses a privacy policy that provides the ability to opt-out of such disclosures to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, then the company is not required to maintain and provide such lists, and instead may provide you with information on how to exercise your right to prevent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. Because coverawards.com’s policy as disclosed on this Site provides you with an opportunity to opt-out of disclosures by coverawards.com of your Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, coverawards.com does not have to provide you with such lists. If you are a California resident who would like information on how to exercise your rights concerning third party disclosures, you may send an email to:

Or contact us via postal mail at:  
California Privacy Rights Information  
coverawards.com  
c/o Tecktonic Media  
48 West 21st Street, Suite 906  
New York, NY 10011  
Attn: California Privacy Rights Administrator

**Collection of Information**  
Information You Provide to Us: Coverawards.com collects information about you that you choose to provide us when you visit and/or purchase products from our websites, subscribe to our magazines, sign up for e-newsletters, enter a contest, participate in surveys, register for a web site, web cast or event; create a member profile or otherwise communicate with us online. Some of this information is automatically collected, and some is collected when you interact with our Site. The type of information that is automatically collected can include date and time of access of the Site, the Internet protocol address of the computer that you are using, the domain and host from which you access the Internet, your browser software and operating system, and the specific activities you are engaged in while visiting the site. Personal Information, including your name, postal address, and e-mail address, may also be collected by coverawards.com at the Site. Of course, you may choose not to provide certain information to coverawards.com, but if so, you may not be able to participate in certain coverawards.com activities and transactions.

To view or change your member profile, please return to the coverawards.com site where you registered and follow the instructions set forth thereon.

**Use of “Cookies” and Other Technologies** : Coverawards.com may use “cookies” and/or other technologies or files (collectively, “cookies”) to identify how its visitors make use of this Site. This aggregate tracking information is used to help coverawards.com improve and enhance the website experience for all of its visitors. The cookies we store on your computer are not accessible on any other companies’ websites.

Additionally, some ads on our Site are provided by outside companies. If these ads contain cookies, only those advertisers can access them; coverawards.com does not have access to the cookies of these advertisers.

If you would prefer not to have such cookies stored on your computer, you may modify your browser settings to reject most cookies, or manually remove cookies that have been placed on your computer. However, by so rejecting the cookies, you may be unable to fully access the offerings on this Site.

**Pixel Tags** : Like many websites, coverawards.com may use pixel tags, also known as web beacons, clear gifs, or web bugs. Pixel tags help us improve our understanding of our web traffic and visitor behavior, as well as gauge the response to our promotional efforts. This information is non-personally identifiable and is used for an aggregate picture of how visitors use our Site.

If you wish, you may disable pixel tags by setting your browser to omit images and disable Javascript.

**Online Ad Serving** : Coverawards.com uses industry-standard, third party advertising service companies to deliver advertisements when you visit our Site or open our emails. These companies may use cookies and pixel tags to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our Site and to other web sites to provide you with relevant advertisements about products, services, and events during your visit to our Site. They can also provide us with aggregate pictures of traffic patterns, help us improve site experience, help advertisers better understand our services, and monitor advertising efforts.

For information about the how to opt out of specific advertisers’ information tracking and collection processes in conjunction with links, online ads, etc., please visit such advertisers’ websites.

**E-mail Communication** : When you communicate with coverawards.com electronically, via e-mail or otherwise, you consent to coverawards.com’s use of the information you have provided, and you further consent to receive electronic communications from coverawards.com. If you would prefer not to receive such communications, please e-mail and so advise.

E-mail Newsletters: If you wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for your contact information (such as name and e-mail address) and information about your geographic region, professional interests, and responsibilities. By completing the required forms and providing them to coverawards.com , you consent to coverawards.com ’s use and sharing of the information you have provided, and you further consent to receive electronic communications from coverawards.com You may also opt out of receiving these communications at any time by sending an e-mail to Privacycoordinator@coverawards.com with your request.

Registration and Ordering: When participating in our customer-sponsored webcasts, entering online contests and giveaways, using certain website functionality, and signing up for certain selected online services (such as free subscriptions), you must first register. During registration, you are required to provide contact information (such as name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number). Upon completing registration, you consent to coverawards.com ’s use and sharing of the information you have provided, and you further consent to receive communications from Coverawards.com If you would prefer not to receive such communications, please e-mail your request to Privacycoordinator@coverawards.com. For our services that require payment (such as certain events, products and subscriptions), we also collect credit card information (such as account name, number and expiration date), which is used for billing purposes only, and is not otherwise shared.

**Security of Information**  
Coverawards.com maintains reasonable standards of confidentiality and security for this Site and the Personal Information collected from this Site. The Personal Information you provide is secured using industry standard e-commerce security technology. Coverawards.com also restricts its own employees’ access to Personal Information. However, it is possible that someone may intercept or access communications, transmissions and/or Personal Information. You must also seek to protect against unauthorized access to any passwords and/or accounts that you use in connection with this website, and you should remember to log off of the website once you have completed your activities on the Site or if you have decided to step away from your computer. In the event that coverawards.com determines that there has been a security breach resulting the unauthorized disclosure of Personal Information to a third party, coverawards.com will notify consumers whose Personal Information has been so disclosed by posting information on the Site and, if email contact is possible, then also by sending an email advisory with respect to situation.

**Use and Sharing of Information**  
**Use of Personal Information by Coverawards.com** : The Personal Information collected by coverawards.com may be used by coverawards.com for any lawful purpose, including but not limited to, to communicate with you, send notices, respond to your requests, and analyze and improve coverawards.com’s products, its business and/or its service to you. Coverawards.com may use this information to send you e-mail newsletters, promotional offers with respect to goods or services of a particular brand or other types of communications on behalf of coverawards.com and/or its affiliates. All e-mail newsletters and promotional offers will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of receiving future issues of such newsletters or to opt out of receiving future promotional offers with respect to such brand. We may also use your Personal Information to communicate with you to ask for your input to help in our research about our services, events, or products or to provide you with additional information about this Site and about other Tecktonik Media websites, products, services, or events that we think might be of interest to you. In some cases, coverawards.com may also use your Personal Information to send you relevant, carefully screened e-mails or other communications on behalf of reputable third parties. All such communications will provide you with the opportunity to opt out of receiving future third party offers from coverawards.com. You may also, at any time, opt-out of receiving any third-party offers from this Site by sending an e-mail to.

**Disclosure by Coverawards.com of Personal Information to Other Entities**  
Without restriction, coverawards.com may disclose aggregated statistics about visitors to its sites, along with specific information concerning individual visitors of its sites that is not Personal Information, provided that no specific individual can be identified by the information so disclosed. Coverawards.com may sometimes seek to share the Personal Information it has collected with a third party, and may also sometimes seek to share such Personal Information with companies that are affiliated with coverawards.com. Coverawards.com may sometimes use a third party to provide certain services on its behalf, such as processing transactions, sending e-mails, subscription fulfillment, research, list cleansing, postal mailings, fax deployment, telemarketing or performing statistical analyses of activity on our websites. In compliance with privacy laws, we also provide our opt-out lists to third party companies so that they can be suppressed from the communications those companies send on coverawards.com’s behalf. We only deal with third party companies whom we believe share our commitment to privacy and who will keep your information secure. In the event that coverawards.com provides certain of your Personal Information to any such entity, coverawards.com will require that any such entity maintain the confidentiality of (and not further share) the Personal Information that coverawards.com has provided to it. Coverawards.com may sometimes share Personal Information with sponsors of Promotions on the Coverawards.com website, or with or with sponsors or advertisers of “premium” content. Coverawards.com will always disclose when you are registering for such a Promotion or requesting such content.

**Accessing Your Information**  
You may update and/or correct the Personal Information collected on this Site, or seek to have such information removed from coverawards.com’s records by contacting us at:

coverawards/com  
c/oTecktonik Media  
48 West 21st Street, Suite 906  
New York, NY 10010

and instructing us as to what type of changes need be made.

**Acquisition of Business**  
In the event that coverawards.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, consolidation, restructuring, reorganization, liquidation, sale or similar transaction relating to any portion of its business and/or assets, you hereby acknowledge and agree that the Personal Information that coverawards.com has collected may be included in the assets, and/or transferred pursuant to, such transaction. If that occurs, coverawards.com will post a notice to such effect on this website.

**Legal Process**  
Coverawards.com may disclose your Personal Information if it has a reasonable good faith basis to believe that it is required to do so by law, compelled by court order or legal process, or is reasonably necessary and/or appropriate to: (i) protect the rights, property and/or safety of coverawards.com or of any other person or entity; or (ii) prevent or take action concerning any alleged: (a) illegal activity or (b) breach of the Terms and Conditions or Privacy Policy of this website.

**Linked Sites**  
From time to time, the coverawards.com website may contain links to other websites that are not controlled and/or maintained by coverawards.com. Please be aware that these other websites may have different privacy policies which may subject you to different privacy practices. Please review the privacy policies of such other websites for information concerning what information is collected on such sites and how it is used.

**Changes in Policy**  
From time to time, coverawards.com’s Privacy Policy may change. Coverawards.com will post changes to the Privacy Policy at this site. Please review this Privacy Policy often so that you will remain abreast of coverawards.com’s current policies, including its policies concerning the gathering and use of information that may be collected on our Site.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 14, 2008 and is effective immediately.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy other than with respect to California Privacy rights, please contact us at:  
Coverawards.com  
c/o Tecktonik Media  
48 West 21st Street, Suite 906  
New York, NY 10010  
Attn: Privacy Coordinator 

**Governing Law**  
This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of New York, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Any dispute concerning this Privacy Policy or your use of this Site shall be submitted to binding arbitration in New York within one (1) year from the date that the cause of action arose (or, if multiple cause of actions are involved, from the date that the first cause of action arose), with such arbitration conducted pursuant to the then prevailing rules of the American Arbitration Association. To the fullest extent permitted by law, no arbitration brought pursuant hereto shall be joined to any other action or any other arbitration initiated pursuant hereto. In the event that any portion of these Terms and Conditions are deemed unenforceable, unlawful or void by a Court of competent jurisdiction, in any jurisdiction for any reason because of the scope, duration or area of its applicability or for other reasons, unless narrowed by construction, such provision shall for purposes of such jurisdiction only, be construed as if such invalid, prohibited or unenforceable provision had been more narrowly drawn so as not to be invalid, prohibited or unenforceable (or if such language cannot be drawn narrowly enough, the court making any such determination shall have the power to modify, to the extent necessary to make such provision or provisions enforceable in such jurisdiction, such scope, duration or area or all of them, and such provision shall then be applicable in such modified form). If, notwithstanding the foregoing, any such provision would be held to be invalid, prohibited or unenforceable in any jurisdiction for any reason, such provision, as to such jurisdiction only, shall be ineffective to the extent of such invalidity, prohibition or unenforceability, without invalidating the remaining provisions. No narrowed construction, court-modification or invalidation of any provision shall affect the construction, validity or enforceability of such provision in any other jurisdiction. No waiver by coverawards.com of any term or condition of these Terms and Conditions shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or of any other term, and Coverawards.com ’s failure to assert any right or demand compliance with any provision of these Terms and Conditions shall not be deemed to constitute a waiver of any such right or provision.

TM and Copyright 2008 Mark Allen & Company LLC. All rights reserved.
